hi my name is Matt I'm a current
strategy and operations associate at
Google and prior to that was a
Management Consultant at BCG and today
we're going to go through a ban and
Company case example that they actually
have on their website I have my laptop
right here with the case pulled up right
here it's called coffee shop co and
let's dive right into it so the
background of the client is that a
friend comes to you for business advice
so you're having lunch with an old
friend from University and she's looking
for some business advice she is thinking
of opening a coffee shop in Cambridge
England a large University City an hour
and a half away from London now she sees
potential in this business but wants
your help in determining whether opening
a coffee shop is a good idea what do you
think so I want to walk you through
essentially what goes through my mind
when I receive a prompt like that and so
typically I have a piece of paper pulled
up and that's what's going to be
happening with you when you're in an
interview because you're going to have a
piece of paper and you're going to be
ideally taking notes and so we need to
take notes on what the problem is so the
problem for my understanding just having
read it is friend is asking us for
advice right and it's specifically
should he or she open the coffee shop in
Cambridge England so should friend open
a coffee shop in Cambridge England all
right so you should always write down
the initial question or the initial
problem that you're trying to solve
because what I found found is that it
can be very easy to get lost in the
details when you're doing a case and
sometimes completely forget what the
initial problem that you were even
solving for was and so if we just write
it at the top of our paper or wherever
maybe in the corner then we can always
go back to it and reference it and we
won't run the risk of accidentally
forgetting what the original question is
and then having to Reas the interviewer
which obviously isn't a very good
look what's up guys just wanted to pop
in here and let you know that I'm
starting a community for people who are
interested in consulting or strategy
roles if you're currently a student or
maybe an early working professional
who's thinking about making a transition
soon you'll find this community really
helpful I'll be in there every week
hosting weekly group calls and you'll be
able to interact with a lot of other
people in a similar position as you if
that sounds interesting then make sure
to check out the link in the description
below and I'll see you on the inside and
so what's going through our mind is when
I reread this question should my friend
open a coffee shop in Cambridge England
there's a bunch of questions that are
going through my head right specifically
if you think about like opening a coffee
shop is one thing but then like in
Cambridge England is another thing and
so there's like two components here
where like component one is like things
that you should consider when you're
just opening a coffee shop in general
and then component two is like what are
the subcategories of things that we need
to consider because we're in Cambridge
England specifically which is its own
City and distinct from other locations
across the world and so starting with
this first part I would want to think
about okay what are the things that we
need to think about when opening a
coffee shop well the first one we can
think of is obviously location but
that's kind of covered that'll be
covered in the next set of questions
related to Cambridge England but also
you want to think about things like
startup costs what are going to be the
operational needs and needs could be
things like obviously raw materials
right the coffee beans but it could also
be like labor for example people that
you would need to hire to run your
coffee shop and then you know there's a
number of other things we could
brainstorm as well but this is kind of
how I start thinking about potential
clarifying questions I break down from
the sentence from the problem statement
what the main components are and in this
case there's two which is generally
opening coffee shop and then the second
is in this specific location and so then
I start brainstorming different things
that I think are important to consider
related to each of these so I've
brainstormed a few related to just
generally opening coffee shop but if we
were to take this location bucket and
really break it down even further
clarifying questions related to
Cambridge England would be like what's
the population of Cambridge England or
like what kind of demographic resides in
Cambridge England right because
different cities are made up of
different groups of people and different
groups of people have different
behavioral characteristics some people
drink a lot of coffee some people don't
drink any coffee Some people prefer to
drink tea over coffee so there's a lot
of things related to the
demographics and demographics is similar
to I'll just say SL Customer because the
people that live there are ideally going
to be the customers when it's a coffee
shop and so we need to understand who
lives there and what the breakdown is
and I think that's the most important
thing when it comes to thinking about a
location is like who lives there
especially we're thinking about a coffee
shop but let's think about specific
clarifying questions now that you could
derive from this set of considerations
that I've just
off the top of my head come up with and
I want to caveat also that this is by no
means an exhaustive list there's
probably other things that I'll think of
after I finished recording and uploading
this video but that's not the point of
the video the point of the video is to
show you my thought process and how I go
about it and so let's just now go ahead
and take what we have and brainstorm a
few questions so this first one here
which is like what's the population
demographic could be one question of
like and I'll just write clarifying
questions here so we'll write them all
down here so first question could be how
big is the population and then a
followup to that could be like what is
or actually let's just say who lives
there okay so that could be a clarifying
question right there and then going back
up to these other considerations related
to just opening a coffee shop in general
we can come up with a few other
questions too like how much is it going
to cost what will it take to let's just
use the word operate right and so here
are two very good clarifying questions
to start with already and see we've
taken this vague question of should your
friend open a coffee shop in Cambridge
England and we've already broken it down
into two or I would say more like four
questions that if we can get some kind
of detail or some kind of an answer
doesn't even have to be a super high
level of detail it'll already help us to
understand a little bit better whether
or not it's a good or bad idea to open
up a coffee shop and so in an interview
scenario you basically want to present
these questions to your interviewer
after you've written them down you want
to say something like awesome so just to
make sure I understood correctly it
sounds like the problem here is that our
friend wants to open a coffee shop or at
least is considering opening a coffee
shop in Cambridge England and they've
come to us to ask us what the key
considerations are and if they should
open up that coffee shop and so a couple
clarifying questions before we get into
it how big is the population would be
curious to understand who actually lives
in Cambridge England and what the
demographic looks like and also just
curious about how much it'll cost for us
to open up a new coffee shop I would
imagine there's some kind of upfront
capital investment that needs to be made
because you don't just open up a coffee
shop you need to get the funds from
either the bank out of your own pocket
or you you know somebody else who's
funding this Venture and so it's
important to understand how much it'll
cost and also related to that how much
is it going to take from a resource
perspective to actually operate this
coffee shop once we've gotten it up and
running and once we have this business
in place is it even going to be
profitable and so that's kind of the way
you want to go about it and in this
situation since I do have the answers
here but I'm going to walk you through
how this would typically go the
interviewer basically has some responses
to some of the clarifying questions that
you have and they might respond
basically to the question that you have
with either specific answers or specific
details related to each question or they
might just kind of answer in a
deliberately vague way which should
indicate to you that maybe there isn't
any follow-up data to that specific
clarifying question and maybe it's not
as important to consider in this case
but but anyway once you've done that and
you've had a bit of a back and forth
with the interviewer about the
clarifying questions then it's time to
go into developing the framework and so
this is something that
sometimes intimidates people because
they either don't understand what a
framework is or they don't really know
if their framework is good and so to
answer the first part of the question a
framework very simply put is just a set
of buckets of different areas or topics
that you think are most important to
consider in order to develop a
recommendation that you feel confident
in and so what makes a good versus a bad
framework though that's highly
subjective but there are certain
principles that apply that make certain
Frameworks better than others and the
most common principle that people are
taught is the Mei principle which simply
stands for mutually exclusive and
collectively exhaustive mutually
exclusive meaning that the components in
your framework the buckets don't have
any kind of overlap so if it was a vend
diagram it wouldn't have any overlap and
collectively exhaustive meaning that the
topics AKA these buckets are all of the
buckets or at least they Encompass all
of the
potential problems or Solutions
available so that you don't accidentally
Overlook something right because you
could have a mutually exclusive
framework but if it doesn't Encompass
the entire universe of possibilities
then you might be missing out on
something that's actually the solution
and so this is the principle that
everyone is basically taught if you
looked at any kind of case interview
guides or you've read any books on how
to do case interviews you'll hear this
term being thrown about all the time oh
yeah you need to be mey you need to make
sure that your framework is perfectly
mey now I'm going to go out on a limb
and say that yes it's good to be mey
generally but it's okay if your
framework is not 100% mey And before you
go Matt what are you talking about
you've no idea what you're saying I just
want to point out that there are a lot
of Frameworks that aren't 100% mey and I
won't get into the details in this video
but as long as your framework is like
covering 90% of things and specifically
as long as it's covering the most
important things to the case then you're
totally fine so don't agonize too much
over being mey but use it as like a
general guiding principle but anyways
now we have to come up with our
framework and so I'm going to erase all
of this but I'm going to leave our key
question at the top so we can again
remind ourselves of what we're trying to
solve for and so if we want to be
totally mey though an easy way to start
is to do something that is opposite so
using the Opposites principle so for
example an easy one is financial factors
versus non-financial factors right
because these are opposites it's either
going to be a financial factor or it's
going to be a non-financial factor
you're mey now once you get past this
first layer though I'd argue you don't
need to be as mey it's okay if there's
like some things that are in your
buckets that aren't complet Macy because
at the end of the day it's going to be
almost impossible to come up with a 100%
Macy framework especially under time
constraints of having like a minute to
come up with this framework in a case so
realistically just try to make sure that
the first layer of your framework is
mostly mey and then the things that you
put under it so for example I'm going to
put a bunch of examples here now those
don't necessarily need to be that mey I
know this might sound a little bit
controversial but I'm all about being
practical here and like 90% of people
when you only have a minute to do this
you're not going to be able to like
spend so much time and effort making
everything perfect and that's just not
realistic we want to have an 8020
mindset here so all right let's think
about some Financial factors so
Financial factors first one I can think
of is capex capital expenditures upfront
investment that is needed to start up
the business whether it's like
purchasing equipment or even like maybe
buying the building that the coffee shop
is is even though realistic you'd
probably just rent but just giving some
examples here actually what I'm going to
do here is I'm going to break this into
a revenue cost thing so revenue and then
cost drivers and then costs would be
fixed versus variable and then Revenue
would be price and then like volume
factors so now surprisingly this is
still mey but anything that would
influence price volume fixed versus
variable costs these are all going to
fall into the financial bucket and so
let's just brainstorm a few here so
fixed cost would be things like capex as
I mentioned The Upfront investment
that's needed because that doesn't
change with volume same with things like
utilities right because it doesn't
matter how many customers or how many
cups of coffee you sell you're still
going to have to pay the same amount of
electricity or generally speaking your
utilities is going to stay roughly
around the same regardless of how many
customers are coming through your doors
and then let's bring some some variable
costs so this is pretty easy this is
like coffee SL like any inputs raw
materials and I would say wages or labor
to pay your employees would probably
fall under I want to say fixed but it
can be a little bit fuzzy because if you
want to open your shop for more hours
then obviously the labor cost goes up
but it doesn't go up with how much
volume of coffee you're selling and so
I'm going to put it in this fixed cost
bucket but if somebody disagrees feel
free to call me out in the comments um
you guys keep me honest so anyways with
price this is just like what are we
pricing it at right and then volume is
going to be just how many cups are we
actually selling but now let's get to
non-financial factors and this is where
I think it will get kind of interesting
so the first one I'm going to put is
customer now the reason I chose customer
is because 99% of the time you want to
have some kind of a customer bucket in
your framework because customer is
important to the business you don't have
a business if you don't have a customer
and so if you're not thinking about what
the customer wants and who the customer
even is then what you have no business
running a business and so on the
customer side we can think about okay
what are their preferences what do they
even care about what do they even want
and then segmentation of the customer
base now I know segmentation sounds like
a fancy word but management Consultants
always use this word and it simply means
what is the breakdown of the customer
base of your entire customer population
the people that buy coffee from you what
percentage of those are male versus
female what percentage of those are age
50 plus or age 20 and Below what
percentage of that population is a
frequent coffee drinker versus a
non-frequent coffee drinker versus a
non- coffee drinker if that's even
possible for a coffee shop maybe you
sell tea and so they buy tea from you
but just understanding how your customer
base can be chopped up by various
segments is going to be critically
important for us to be successful and so
that's the customer bucket now the next
bucket I want to consider is competition
actually I'm going to name this bucket
the market bucket now the reason for
this is because the market can be split
into two things size SLG growth and then
also competition and under size SLG
growth this is simply understanding how
big is the market for coffee from a
coffee shop in Cambridge England and is
that market growing or is it shrinking
if it's growing and it's massive then
that's amazing but it's not necessarily
a bad thing if it's not growing because
maybe there's very little competition so
there's still opportunity for us to take
share and to grow our business but this
is why competition is important because
we need to understand who is the
competition and what's the concentration
of competitors in other words not just
thinking about like physically like are
they concentrated as in like is there a
coffee shop on every corner like there
is in New York City but what is the
market share concentration by
competitors so is there one guy like
Starbucks who's taking up half the
market and then the rest is like a bunch
of random no-name dinky local coffee
shops I have nothing against local
coffee shops by the way I love local
coffee shops but just giving an example
or is this Market completely just
fragmented and filled up with a bunch of
small players and there's nobody who has
over 20% market share understanding
these things are going to be very
important because it's going to
influence whether or not we actually
want to go ahead and open our own coffee
shop if there's only two or three
massive competitors and they have like
basically the whole market then it might
be very difficult for us to actually
compete effectively and to enter as a
new player now there's a counterargument
to that which you could say like oh we
can come on we can come in and be a
disruptor and we can you know if we have
some unique value proposition and some
unique product then we can disrupt the
market we can disrupt the incumbents now
that can be true if you're in Tech or
maybe Healthcare but not coffee coffee
is a little bit tougher because there's
limited differentiation in the product
but that's besides the point so broadly
speaking let's go through the framework
again I've bucketed by Financial factors
versus non-f Financial factors under my
financial factors I've broken it into
revenue and cost under my non-financial
factors I've broken it into customer and
market now there could be a few other
things that I put in this non-financial
bucket for example I could do something
like risks so this bucket is going to be
basically encompassing things that could
potentially go wrong and so a couple
things I can think of are executional
risk which is what if even though we
have the perfect plan we fail to
actually execute on that plan which is a
very real problem for businesses another
thing could be macro risk like what if
all of a sudden the price of coffee
beans skyrockets and then it becomes
impossible expensive to sell coffee and
then we go bankrupt that is a real risk
and so that could be another thing now
we could brainstorm a few other risks
here but I want to just finalize this
section and just show you that okay this
framework right here although it is not
100% mey it is mey at the first level
and then it hits on the most important
buckets at the next level and that's
what matters you need to be able to have
a conversation with your interviewer
about
okay customer okay Market okay risks
related to this because the next thing
you need to do after you come up with
this framework is you need to walk them
through your thought process and you
need to say awesome so I've taken some
time now to put together a framework and
I'd like to walk you through it broadly
speaking I've split the key
considerations into two main buckets the
first being Financial considerations the
second being non-financial
considerations and to walk you through
each of these buckets now in the first
bucket here I'm curious about factors
that influence revenue and factors that
influence cost and in the non-financial
bucket what I think is most important is
to consider who the customer is what the
market looks like and what the key risks
are related to actually starting and
running this business and then you can
just go down the list and so after you
walk the interviewer through the
framework because this is a bane case
that means that it's probably going to
be interviewee Leed which means that
it's on you to basically push the case
forward what you should do is you should
suggest a bucket that you think is the
most important to consider
or where you just like to start okay
don't overthink this part some people
stress a lot over oh did I pick the
right bucket just pick one that feels
important to you and then just push it
forward so say something like okay so
those are the buckets that again I'm
thinking about considering I'd like to
start with the market bucket because I
think it's really important to
understand first of all the market in
Cambridge England and who the customers
are there who the competitors are and
how big the market even is right and so
based on what you say the interviewer
should react and you have to be really
perceptive to how they react because if
they react in a way where they're like
oh yeah yeah that's you know makes total
sense to me we actually have some data
related to that then you know you're in
the right direction but if they say
something a little bit more vague and
they kind of sound like they're trying
to dissuade you from going in that
direction then don't push and just
realize that it's probably not a
direction that the case is supposed to
go in and I know some of you might be
thinking what the heck like these case
interviews they're supposed to test my
problem solving ability but it seems
like there's only one right solution and
in some ways yes it is a little bit
frustrating sometimes when you think
that one bucket is the most important to
consider but then you get pushed in
another Direction but just go with it
okay you need to be able to roll with
the punches and at the end of the day
you really only have like 30 minutes in
an interview and so there's not a ton of
time to just debate what the most
important consideration is but anyways
in this case just moving along here so
the case reads you show your proposed
framework to your friend and she really
likes it she's especially interested in
figuring out how big the market is to
best estimate how much coffee she can
sell she knows the market probably
includes commuters visitors Etc but for
now she wants you to focus on Cambridge
residents alone how do you estimate the
size of the market amazing so we've
basically found ourselves entering into
the next phase of the case which is a
market sizing question and so maybe I'll
just use the left side of the board here
so Market sizing the first thing you
always want to do when you're working on
a market sizing problem is you need to
think about first what the question is
but then ways that you can clarify the
question so there will always be ways
that you can clarify the question the
question in this case is what is the
market for coffee in Cambridge England
and some of you might be thinking wow
that's already pretty specific what do
you mean let me tell you so there's a
couple things that we could clarify here
the first is what do you mean when it's
the market is that like number of cups
of coffee being sold or is that dollar
value you need to always clarify that
then second is when we say for coffee is
this like coffee beans or is it like
cups of coffee that are sold in
commercial
cafes because somebody could go to
Walmart and buy a bunch of coffee beans
so we need to clarify like is this
actual cups sold at cafes or is it
something else and then even within
Cambridge England this you could clarify
this and say okay is this like the
actual City proper or is it the entire
surrounding metro area right because if
I think about I live in New York I don't
know what it's like in Cambridge England
somebody correct me wrong but in New
York for example a lot of people when
they think about New York City they're
referring to Manhattan which is only one
of the five burrows New York is actually
much bigger than Manhattan and so just
clarifying that would dramatically
influence the outcome of the sizing and
so we need to be very thoughtful about
okay what can we actually clarify here
and that's how you want to be thinking
about it and so don't assume that
anything is given you always want to be
questioning things okay and so for
Market sizing questions there's two
approaches that we could take one is we
could do a what's known as a top- down
approach which is when you basically
start with a very big number usually the
population and then you work your way up
to that big number now nine times out of
10 I would recommend you go with top
down not bottoms up because top down is
usually a little bit easier to due to
the fact because top down because in my
experience usually the interviewer will
have some kind of like very big juicy
population number or some number that
you can then use to whittle down slowly
to your actual Market size and so you
can ask your interviewer hey do we have
any information related to say the
population of the city or any other data
points related to the market and they
may or may not give you information that
can indicate whether or not you should
do a top down or a bottom up but I would
say nine times out of 10 is going to be
a top down and so today I'm going to
walk you through how I would think
through a top down approach so in this
scenario once you do ask the interviewer
these clarifying questions they are
going to tell you that yes this is the
city of Cambridge England you are
actually solving for volume so it's cups
of coffee and yes it is cups that are
sold at cafes okay so the way I am
thinking about this is we probably want
to start with a tops down approach so
we're going to start with a population
number and then we need to determine how
many people actually drink coffee so
number of coffee Drinkers and then we
need to get to like how many cups of
coffee these people are actually
drinking and of those how many of those
cups that were drank were drank at cafes
as opposed to being brewed at home which
wouldn't be a part of this Market sizing
exercise and only once we do all of that
will we get to units of coffee sold at
cafes on an annual basis and the
interviewer is going to give you two
pieces of information after you walk him
through his approach he's going to
basically tell you that look we have a
population number of 100,000 people and
we know that on average they're actually
drinking one cup per day okay and so now
let's go back through and let's think
about how we can actually do this math
so one distinction I want to make is
that we have to make some assumptions
here around how many people are actually
drinking coffee because we know that
there's 100,000 people living in
Cambridge but let's think about this
usually only adults are the ones that
are drinking coffee kids and babies
don't really drink coffee and so some
percentage are going to be adults which
let's assume 80% are adults which gets
us 80k so there's 80k adults but let say
that only half of them are actually
coffee drinkers so times 50% which is
40k so apologies for this messy math but
40K coffee drinkers now they drink one
cup of coffee per day so that's 40K cups
still but what percentage of those cups
are being sold in cafes versus brewed at
home and this is where because I have
the answer I'm going to look at it and
I'm going to see that roughly
50% of cups of coffee are sold at cafes
versus bred at home now even though I
had the answer in a case interview
scenario it's totally okay to make an
assumption here as long as it's baked in
some kind of rationale so you should be
able to say okay based on my knowledge
having gone to some coffee shops and as
a coffee drinker myself it sounds
reasonable to me that half of the cups
of coffee that people are consuming
would be sold at cafes versus brood at
home because if I think about from my
experience I drink maybe 10 cups of
coffee a week and half those are from my
local Starbucks half of those I brew in
my dorm room something like that as long
as you say it confidently and make it
convincing as long as it's not totally
out of whack then you're fine with the
assumptions and you're not being tested
on the assumptions as much as you're
being tested on the actual methodology
and the equation that you've come up
with and so again we have 20K cups of
coffee that are being produced at cafes
and we need to still annualize this
though because remember this is on a
daily basis and so to get to an annual
number we need to multiply this 20K by
the number of days in a year now in this
case let's round to 350 instead of 365
because it makes the math a little bit
easier and so 20K times 350 days per
year is going to get us roughly 7
million cups in a year and so I don't
know if you can see that but this is our
Market size 7 million cups and so the
first thing you should do after you come
up with this number is you need to take
a step back ins sanity check your
numbers and think about is this
reasonable does this feel reasonable to
me and try to think aloud and give your
interviewer your initial reaction and
show them what you're thinking and you
want to say something about okay so it
looks like we've come up to a number of
7 million cups of coffee on an annual
basis as the market size for coffee sold
in cafes in Cambridge England and it is
a little bit tough given that I don't
have any reference points to compare
this number to but 7 million cups sounds
reasonable to me given what I know
something like that ideally you have
another number to compare it to but you
won't always have this and single data
points are tough because they don't
really mean anything in isolation unless
you can look at some other number to get
a sense of the size and the scale but
basically after you do this you're going
to move to the next part of the question
and the interviewer is going to push you
to this point which is now that you have
the market size your friend wants to
gain a better understanding of how much
coffee she would need to sell to break
even in her first year and so the
interviewer is actually going to give us
some additional information here for
this break even analysis and so they're
going to tell us that the price that
we're selling coffee at
is3 per cup the cost to run the shop is
245,000
610 British pounds or sorry that's
actually the cost to open the shop so
that's your upfront capex and then
there's a cost to actually run the shop
each year which is going to be
163,944
pound per cup and so they just want to
know how many cups of coffee does your
friend need to sell in order to break
even in year one I'm going to write year
one up here and it's always important to
clarify if they don't give you the time
frame under which you're supposed to be
calculating this break even because
Break Even under what like one year two
years 5 years it could mean a lot of
things and so it's important to clarify
again what the time frame is and so what
I'm going to do here is I'm first going
to calculate the variable profit which
we can see is simply or the profit per
cup which is simply two 2B per cup and
then we have a bunch of these fixed
costs right here right so we have like
the cost to open the shop plus the cost
to run the shop now the total if we sum
up these two fixed cost buckets right
here is going to be roughly and I'll
just put it down here 4, $
49,3 yeah and so all we need to do is
take this number and divide it by the
variable profit per cupy which is
dividing by two in order to get to our
break even and again reminding you that
this is the year one break even which is
why we've added these two numbers
together because you're going to open it
and then you're going to have to run it
for a year and so in year one you incur
both of these costs and so if we divide
this by two what we get is
204,000
675 should be British pounds but I put a
dollar sign by accident so that's how
many cups of coffee she needs to sell in
year one in order to just break even not
even to make like a significant profit
and so what you should do again is you
should look at this number and you
should think to yourself and think aloud
to your interviewer about what this
means and whether or not you think this
is achievable or not whether or not you
think it's reasonable you should say
something like okay so it sounds like we
have to produce
204,000 cups of coffee in year one in
order to just break even now do I think
this is reasonable does it sound
reasonable to me I think that given that
the market for coffee cups in Cambridge
England is 7 million then this
200,000 is just a small drop in the
bucket of that 7 million in fact if we
were to do some quick math I mean 200k
over 7 million is less than
5% of the entire market so I think it's
quite attainable at least given what I
know and so this is the part of the case
where now the interview is going to push
you to come to a final recommendation
and move you on to the synthesis
synthesis simply meaning taking all of
the information that you've gathered
today and combining it into a concise
recommendation and the process that I
always like to suggest people follow is
you want to start with your
recommendation you want to follow up
with some risks then you want to end
with next steps and I'll show you why in
a second and so you want to take a
minute and you want to basically think
through everything that you've learn
learn today all the analysis that you've
done all of the data and the information
that you've gathered and you want to
just think about a defensible
recommendation that you can come with
and so in our scenario what we could say
to our friend is hey so I've taken some
time to think about whether or not it
makes sense for you to open up a coffee
shop in Cambridge England and after
doing some analysis I think it makes
sense for you to go ahead with opening
up this coffee shop because I've done
some market research and you would only
need to sell about 200,000 cups of
coffee in your first year which is only
about 5%
in order to break even and to make a
profit and given what I know about the
market there is for example no major
players that are greater than 20% market
share on making this up but assuming
that you had learned that in the case
and so I think that it's a good idea for
you to go ahead with doing this now that
said there are a number of risks as well
including actually being able to execute
on running this coffee shop successfully
there could be some legal issues as well
when we're trying to open up a new store
and there could be issues with our
customers just not liking our coffee and
so as a potential poal Next Step what I
would recommend is for us to understand
these risks a little bit better we
should probably do some customer
research to understand what people are
looking for in Cambridge England when it
comes to coffee shops and also probably
looking into the legal considerations of
how do we actually open up a new
business in this specific City and so
that's the case let me know what you
think in the comments below and I'll see
you guys in the next one thanks